[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of a medicinal mud?",
   "Answer": "Fango"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What do you call a native of Kenya?",
   "Answer": "Kenyan"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "What is the official language in Kosovo?",
   "Answer": "Albanian"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Which weekday is domingo in Spanish and dimanche  in French?",
   "Answer": "Sunday"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What do you call a motorcycle with four wheels?",
   "Answer": "Quad"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "How do you say AIDS in French?",
   "Answer": "Sida"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "What is the meaning of the Arab word Habibi?",
   "Answer": "Sweetheart"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What does the abbreviation GPS mean?",
   "Answer": "Global Positioning System"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most spoken language in the world?",
   "Answer": "Chinese language"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "What does the abbreviation SMS mean?",
   "Answer": "Short Message Service"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is another word for wall painting or mural?",
   "Answer": "Fresco"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Which language group includes Irish, Welsh and Breton?",
   "Answer": "Celtic languages"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "What is the meaning of the following abbreviation: IBM?",
   "Answer": "International Business Machines"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What is the islamic term for fast?",
   "Answer": "Ramadan"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What is the much nicer name for the dung beetle, which was used in the ancient Egypt?",
   "Answer": "Scarab"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the Turkish word for lamb?",
   "Answer": "Kebab"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is the Spanish word for black?",
   "Answer": "Negro"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What does glasnost mean in Russian politics?",
   "Answer": "Openness"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "What does the name of the Russian newspaper Pravda mean?",
   "Answer": "Truth"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What does the Latin proverb -Errare Humanum est- mean",
   "Answer": "Err is human"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "To which language is Portuguese closely related?",
   "Answer": "Spanish language"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "What word is used in Hawaii both to greet and to say goodbye?",
   "Answer": "Aloha"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "What is the singular of Scampi ?",
   "Answer": "Scampo"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Which is the world s second largest French-speaking city?",
   "Answer": "Montreal (Canada)"
 }
]